paycor.com 2007-08-08

# Paycor.com Privacy Statement

| 

---  
  
  |  |    
  |  |  |  Paycor Privacy Statement  
---  
Paycor, Inc. values your privacy, and is committed to not only providing exceptional client service but also peace of mind that your business, financial and/or personal information is secure. We use reasonable care to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We have created this privacy statement with your privacy and security in mind. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. This Privacy Statement may be revised from time to time without notice.  
Collecting of Personal Information  
Personal information is only collected when the visitor submits it. Generally, this information is requested when a visitor is asked to register before entering a limited-access site, or when the visitor requests information or contact from Paycor, Inc.  
Cookies  
In an effort to publish content visitors need and want, Paycor collects summative site-visitation statistics using cookies. A cookie is a piece of data that our Web site may provide to your browser while you are at our site. We do not track individuals use of the site. 

When an Internet user visits our site, a cookie is placed on the visitor's machine (if the visitor accepts cookies) or is read if the visitor has accessed the site previously. 

We do not use this technology to develop or access personally identifiable information about the visitor; it is a tool we use to compile statistics about our web site usage. We do not share this information outside of Paycor, and do not allow other companies to place technology on our site that would develop personally identifiable information. 

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the paycor.com web site, you will be able to view the text and graphics in the public web sites only. Limited-access sites require that the visitor's browser accept cookies.   
  
External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. Paycor is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   
Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We take a number of security precautions to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of our data. These precautions can be grouped as internal security and external security. Both security groups define the individuals or groups who are authorized to access and/or change data. This prevents unauthorized individuals from accessing, copying, editing, or deleting private data. We also implement an audit system that tracks access, both successful and unsuccessful, to confidential data. This audit information is used to constantly evaluate and refine our security measures and to identify individuals who might attempt to inappropriately access data and to take remedial action.  
Data Quality/Access  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:  
  
  1. You can send email to [ Internet Support](http://www.paycor.com/contact/mailform.asp)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:   
Paycor, Inc., 644 Linn Street, Suite 200, Cincinnati, OH 45203 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 800.381.0053 
  4. You can contact your specialist or new account coordinator

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us through [ Internet Support](http://www.paycor.com/contact/mailform.asp)  

  |    
| Copyright © 2006 Paycor, Inc. All rights reserved.   
---
